You live in this world,
you make choices.
Choices you try to justify.
For yourself, for your family.
And for a while, it works.
Until it doesn't.
Until you make a choice
that renders everything worthless.
One you can't justify.
Can't forgive.
And it takes everything.
Your family.
Your friends.
Your self.
And then all you're left with is nothing.
Nothing but ghosts.
Pull over! Stop the truck now!
Pull me in!
Stop your vehicle! Stop your vehicle now!
This is fucked. This is so fucked!
Pull over.
Oh shit! Mia, this side!
Look out!
- Fuck! Pull me in!
- Dude, fucking hell!
Get in, Johnny!
Fuck.
Stop, or we will open fire!
- Gotta lose 'em!
- I'm fucking trying, Charlie!
Well, try harder.
Fucking punch it. Go. Floor it!
They're headed for the fucking freeway.
Go!
Come on!
Oh fuck.
Oh God!
- Jake!
- I can't get him out.
He's fucking breathing that shit in.
Vince, what happened?
Oh God.
Fuck. Fuck!
Zero-six-four.
Officer Cortez down.
Repeat, Officer Cortez down.
We need immediate medical assistance.
We're on Amherst and 16th.
Is this all you got?
Well, yeah. If you're gonna leave it
this late, what do you expect?
Earlier tonight,
the District Attorney announced
they'd be dropping all charges
against mayoral candidate
and real estate mogul, Lawrence Beaumont.
I'm relieved that DA Collins
has finally come to his senses
and realizes that I'm a part
of the solution, not the problem.
- They're all fucking crooked.
- Yeah, no shit.
This once fine city
has become a cesspit of crime,
our streets are awash with drugs,
and he has the temerity
to accuse me of criminality.
- The indictment…
- Can you wrap all of these, please?
You want me to wrap all this?
Yeah.
Where the fuck do you think you are,
FAO Schwarz?
All right, just give me a fucking bag.
No, it's supposed to be a surprise
for under the tree.
How's it gonna be a surprise,
you see through the bag?
Oh, I'm sorry. I've got a newspaper,
but you'll have to pay for that.
Give me the newspaper, some Scotch tape,
I'll wrap it my fucking self.
- How much?
- Thirty bucks.
The deal of the century
for Father of the Year.
- Wow.
Thanks.
Merry Christmas.
…supports our campaign.
Support our campaign
for urban regeneration.
Hey. Yo. It's, uh, it's me.
Yeah, I called you earlier,
but you didn't pick up.
And?
And, uh, I got a little something
for Emmy, uh,
and it's wrapped.
Father of the Year.
Yeah, I heard that.
I was thinking maybe I could come over.
- I could give it to her myself.
- You know what time it is?
- Yeah, it's ten o'clock.
- She's six.
Six-year-olds go to sleep at 7:00.
Nah. Not at Christmas, they don't.
You know what? Yes, Patrick.
Even at Christmastime. What's your point?
Point is, it's super exciting, Christmas.
I used to get excited myself.
- You fucking lie to me every day!
- I used to stay up all night.
Oh, stop fucking crying.
I said open up.
Yo, not right now. I'm busy.
Fuck "busy." It's the police.
Open the door.
You better shut the fuck up, all right?
Just a sec.
Evening, officer. There a problem here?
- Where is she?
- Where's who?
Quit bullshitting me, okay?
I heard a disturbance.
Nah. Can't two people argue no more?
I mean, I didn't call five-oh.
Bitch, you call five-oh?
Mm-mm. No.
Nah, she didn't call,
so… what you doing here?
Open the fucking door.
Yeah, I just want to speak to my daughter.
It's, you know, it's Christmas.
Yeah. You keep saying.
- I'm trying here.
- Showing up with a present doesn't count.
I'm up to my neck in bills.
You can't keep up payments.
Yeah, but I have money.
You know I have money.
We don't want your dirty money.
That dirty money stopped the bank
from foreclosing on the house.
Didn't bother you then.
My salary can't cover these costs.
What do you want me to do?
Don't make me out to be the bad guy.
The money was never the point.
Eighteen months ago,
the man I loved disappeared,
and a year ago, what was left walked out.
No explanation.
All that's on you.
- That's not on me.
- No, but you're putting it on Emmy.
Why don't you put her on the phone?
Ask her if she wants to speak to me?
Because she's six years old.
What do you think she's gonna say?
- "Yeah."
- I said stop!
The fuck?
She fucking tripped me.
Bullshit.
Slipped.
Wait. What are you doing?
I told you to stay in the car.
- You didn't see what was going on.
- It doesn't matter what's going on.
I'm a homicide cop,
which makes you, by association,
now a homicide cop too.
Did someone die in there?
- No, but...
- No?
- If I hadn't...
- Fucking Christ!
You better arrest that asshole.
He beat the shit out of me!
- You see?
- Ain't the first time neither.
You cause these kind of problems.
- Punk-ass bitch.
- No.
- No, you call this in.
- Hey. Wait, wait! Where you going?
- You can't leave me like this!
- Fuck you. Fuck you!
The fuck is this guy?
We can't just be sitting here.
You said we'd walk in,
steal a truckload of washing machines.
- Yeah, that's what we did.
- No, that's not all we did.
I might have killed a fucking cop, man.
All we gotta do is pay off Mia's debt.
Anything else is on me.
Whatever happens, I'll take the rap.
Yeah?
Hey. He's here.
All right.
We're up.
Hey.
We'll be right back.
Okay?
- Boss.
- Hm?
- You made it.
- Yeah, we did.
Just barely.
Come on.
This way.
Open the door.
Man, I gotta say.
I didn't expect you to deliver.
I definitely didn't have you down
for putting a cop in ICU,
with a fucking washing machine.
"I see you."
You can leave us.
- Huh.
- Sorry, boss.
Light.
- Keep a lookout.
- Yes, boss.
What the fuck is that?
No, no, no, we gotta go!
- We've gotta go!
- Turn it off!
Mia, get the fuck out of there now!
I had it handled back there, you know?
So, are they putting, uh, uniform
with homicide now?
I just go where I'm assigned.
You must've pissed somebody off.
Must've shit the bed pretty bad
to get pinned on someone like me.
On the bright side,
you didn't have a partner, and now you do.
No, we're not partners. All right?
Did you get your daughter's gift?
Kinda.
- How old is she?
- Six.
She's, um… She's six.
- And that's all they had?
- Yeah, that's all they had.
Ah, doesn't matter.
When I was a kid, it's always...
Yeah, you know what?
I think we shared just about enough.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Staring. Why are you staring?
Why are you doing that? Don't do that.
Don't look at you when I'm talking to you?
No, don't.
All units, all units, 10-71.
Code purple on Elmore and Fifth.
Yo!
What you got for me?
This way.
Okay, suspects fled up those stairs
through a restaurant full of diners,
jumped in a car.
Nobody got a look at the plates.
We're still piecing together the CCTV
to track their journey. In here.
Okay, thank you.
Oh. All right.
- Hey.
- Yeah, what?
- Sorry about Cortez.
- What do you mean? Detective Cortez?
- Yeah.
- Why? What happened?
- He got hurt in a pursuit earlier.
- What do you mean hurt? What's wrong?
Yeah, he's in surgery.
Vince and the guys are with him.
- I figured they would've told you.
- Nobody told me shit.
It's gonna be okay. He'll pull through.
All right?
Shit.
Sir, we got footage of our suspects.
All right, suspects.
Hey, where's that from?
- Upstairs.
- All right. Got anything from down here?
- No. Nothing down here yet.
- Nothing down here? All right.
- Mm.
- Do you know him?
I don't fucking know him.
I don't know everybody in this city.
Ooh, there's a problem with the suspect.
- Well, she's armed.
- Yeah-huh. But what's she holding?
- A pistol.
- Yeah, a pistol, right.
You see any pistol shells here?
- No.
- No. I don't either.
What do you see? Look around.
What's that? These?
Assault rounds.
I see assault rounds too.
High-velocity assault rounds,
as a matter of fact. So we're looking for…
- An assault rifle.
- Rifle, right.
Do you see an assault rifle?
I don't see a fucking assault rifle.
A lot of dead people here,
never got a shot off.
She supposed to have killed them
with a pea shooter? I don't think so.
Find me an assault rifle.
We may be looking for somebody else.
- Right.
- Yeah, right.
Uh, do we have any cameras
down here at all? Any... any footage?
No, nothing down here.
All right.
And we're saying that they left this way?
Yes. It's been established.
So, who shot up the staircase? Huh?
'Cause someone did.
Look, there's a bunch of shells here too.
- Huh?
- Hey.
- What you got there?
- It's just a mess.
- You got a body to go with this mess?
- No.
All we got's this blood trail
leading up the steps.
It goes cold around the corner.
Maybe they got in a car?
Jesus.
Okay, our John Doe here
must've been working the door.
So I want you to call every ICU.
Probably looking for a male.
Probably Asian. Definitely full
of fucking holes, though, right?
- Right.
- Maybe they have our assault rifle.
- Maybe.
Call me as soon as you have
any updates. All right?
Yes, sir.
I gotta take care of something.
Walker!
We spending Christmas together?
I don't know how you got
that DA off my back, but…
…you gift-wrapped that motherfucker
in a nice pink bow.
Good job.
Where's Charlie?
Charlie and I haven't spoken
since his mother passed, so…
But you know that.
I just came from a crime scene. Right?
Nine bodies.
A coke deal gone bad, real bad.
And then I see this on CCTV. Who's that?
- You recognize that kid?
- Charlie?
You know where he is?
I have no idea.
My son is not a killer.
There is no way that he did this.
Maybe he did. Maybe he fucking didn't.
Doesn't matter. He's in the fucking mix.
- Fuck!
- Yeah, fuck.
Way I see it, your son shit the bed so bad
you'll need a magic wand to clean this up.
- How you gonna get me out of this?
- Are you fucking serious?
I can't help you with this.
Your son just started a gang war.
They wanna shoot him dead.
End of the story.
This whole thing here, your war on drugs,
"cleaning up the city" bullshit,
is over, man. You are done.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
This is my town.
And that's my son we're talking about.
I make one phone call,
you and your friends go down for life.
Don't forget, I know what you did.
Mm. You wanna talk about what I did?
I blackmailed your DA, kept your ass
out of prison. That's what I did.
All right?
We are square, Lawrence. We are good.
When you came to me with this,
you knew exactly
what I was gonna ask you to do.
So don't pretend
that you don't got a price for this.
I do... I do not want your dirty money.
So what do you... what do you...
what do you want from me? Just tell me.
'Cause I'm not gonna let this thing
with my son destroy my campaign.
I do that, and all of this is for nothing.
So tell me.
What do you want?
What can I give you?
I just... I just want you out.
That... that's all.
I just... I want... I'm done. I want…
All right.
Let's say I get your son.
I bring him back to you.
Yeah? I go get him. I bring him to you.
You get him on a plane.
I never see your fucking face again.
There will be no more
running around after that.
That's it, we're done.
We're square.
That's what it will cost.
That could work.
Get him back.
And I never see your fucking face again?
You heard me.
I can work with that.
She's brought her own people.
Welcome, Big Sister.
Who killed my son?
His father's an influential man.
He may not be easy to find.
If you can't find the person
who killed my son…
I'll bury you with him.
I'm begging you. My wife is in hospital.
I don't give a fuck about your wife.
Doesn't stop you
from owing me fucking money.
My fucking nose!
Hey! Hey!
No, no, no!
Get the fuck up.
Do you work for Tsui Fong, huh?
Does he understand me?
Do you work for Tsui Fong?
Are you his doorman?
- Yes.
- Yeah? Yeah!
Yeah! All right, all right. Good. Now…
Do you recognize this guy?
He was at Tsui's last night.
Walked right past you.
You saw him, right?
He says no.
You don't know this guy?
Okay. Let me try and remind you. See this?
Huh?
No, no. You don't get to fall asleep.
No, wake up.
Okay, come on. Back in the room, huh?
You were winning. You were winning, yeah?
Does he remember yet?
- He's seen him with Mr. Tsui.
- All right.
Did he shoot, and did he kill, Tsui Fong?
Did he?
Listen to this man.
But... No.
What's he saying?
He said three demons came.
Demons?
Yeah?
Right. All right.
And I'm a leprechaun,
and I come riding in on a little unicorn
all the way down here.
Huh? Do you understand this? Huh?
You've got to give me
something better than that.
Tell him he's got to do better.
Give me something better.
What is he saying?
I don't understand what you're saying.
Demons in hockey masks.
Demons with hockey masks.
That's… That what I...
That's what I have to work with. That's...
They shot him. They shot Mr. Tsui.
That's all he knows.
Mr. Walker, please. He's gonna die.
You should've called me the moment
this guy walked inside your office.
That's what you're supposed to do.
That's what you get paid for.
Hey. Before you pump people full of drugs.
I can't work with this.
Look at the state of...
I can't do anything with this.
Demons with fucking hockey masks.
Next time, I won't make it
look so convenient.
You fucking rat.
You betrayed me.
You betrayed me!
Hey, Walker.
Good to see you.
How's he doing?
Not great.
Used to be, when one of us got hurt,
the others would drop everything
to be by his side.
- I just heard.
- They got a waiting room.
I'm sorry. It looks like
you got chewed up pretty bad, Jake.
It's kinda hard
to dodge a fucking washing machine.
Hey, come on. We're all hurting.
No one's to blame. Hey.
We missed you.
Everything good at home? Family okay?
Yeah, everyone's good.
Dispatch announced Charlie Beaumont's
public enemy number one.
- You know they ID'd him in Chinatown?
- Mm.
They also got him stealing
that fucking truck we were chasing.
- All right.
- Hope that doesn't put you in a box.
I'm sorry?
Uh, you just lost me there, Vince.
Oh, I doubt that.
No, really. I...
What's that supposed to mean?
We've all done shit for Lawrence,
but that don't give his kid
a free fucking pass
to hurt one of our own.
So what you gonna do?
You gonna shoot him?
Hm?
Mm.
All right, it's been cool.
Great catching up.
If you don't mind,
I'm gonna see our friend.
Angie. Hey.
Walker.
It's so good to see you.
How's he doing?
He's stable.
They…
They don't know if…
Whenhe does wake,
they don't know whether he'll...
He will.
No, don't even think about it.
Hm.
He's always looked up to you.
He even spoke about leaving narcotics.
Joining your unit.
Hm.
He's been unhappy for a while.
I thought it was me at first.
Last night, before he went into surgery,
he was in and out of consciousness.
I couldn't tell if he was delirious,
but he kept talking
about the five of you getting in a mess.
He said some things.
About you.
About Vincent and the guys.
He sounded scared, Walker.
He said something
about how you shouldn't have been there,
that... that he shouldn't have been there.
He said... he said you took care of it.
Hm.
Yeah, I know what he's talking about.
And it has absolutely nothing
to do with him.
That's on me.
And that's on Vincent.
But it has nothing to do with him.
Excuse me, Mrs. Cortez.
May I speak to you in private, please?
Excuse me.
This way, please.
What is it?
Your husband is stable,
his vitals are good,
but he has sustained
significant impact damage…
Guy's carrying fucking wiretaps.
What the fuck
is an undercover cop doing here?
Shit. We need to get him to hospital.
I don't think he's gonna make it.
He's one of us, Vince.
I can't have this on me.
Walker, I'm pretty sure
that's one of the good guys,
and if he did make it,
he'd have a hell of a story to tell.
And I ain't gonna have that on me.
We're taking him. End of discussion.
Fuck.
Mia.
You been on TV all day.
What the fuck?
You want to tell me what happened?
We had no choice! Tsui was gonna kill us
if we didn't do what he asked.
- Just like that?
- Yes! You know how he is!
"Was." He's fucking dead now.
You know, I could get you papers,
but it'd be a whole lot easier
if you was on your own.
Listen.
Your boy Charlie,
he has a very rich father
that can take care of him.
What you got?
This right here. Me. That's it.
Yeah, and that means the world,
tío, but I... So does he.
Okay.
I call you. You don't call me.
Remember that.
I'll have those passports ready
by this evening.
Okay.
Kid.
Be safe.
- Okay.
- Go.
Go, come on.
Get out. Get out of the fucking car!
- Stop resisting!
- Get his fucking arm.
- Fuck!
- I'm trying.
Grab his fucking legs.
What do you mean I can't speak to him?
Jesus.
Yeah.
- Hey, man, that's the captain's.
- Yeah, she won't mind.
- What the hell happened to you?
- You got my assault rifle?
No, but I found this.
What's this?
It's a mask.
Maybe a hockey mask?
- It's got blood on it.
- Yeah.
- You run this?
- Yes, I did.
Yeah, that's good. Look at you, killer.
Yeah. I found that doorman.
You found him?
Mm-hmm.
You had me running around all the ICUs
all day looking for him.
I didn't know I was gonna find him.
What'd he say?
He was talking about demons and dragons,
and shooting up the place.
Demons?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
So you didn't miss much. Who's this?
That's Clarice Fong.
Mother to our dead Triad boss.
She and a bunch of new faces
are in town for the funeral party.
Walker.
Shit.
How's your new partner?
Uh, good. Yeah, good.
Good? Richardson could use her.
What's that supposed to mean?
You knew it was Charlie Beaumont
on that security video,
and you kept it to yourself.
Cortez is fighting for his life.
I thought you'd have more class.
Um… Mm.
We done?
Yeah, we're done.
Ellie, Richardson will be the lead
on this case.
- Report to him immediately.
- Yes, ma'am.
Hey. Hey, you.
Hey, you, come here. Ellie.
- What do you want?
- Tell me what they got on the girl.
- You lied to me.
- I know. Sorry about that.
- Could've trusted me.
- I know. Sorry about that too. All right?
- I need information.
- You don't. You're off the case.
Hey, Richardson's not gonna solve no case.
That's not what's gonna happen.
He'll find two kids dead in a ditch.
All right? That's gonna be on us.
And you know they didn't do it.
She works at a scrapyard
owned by a Raul Vasquez.
- This does not come back to me.
- It won't.
Now, go fuck yourself.
O holy night
The stars are brightly shining
It is the night
Of the dear Savior's birth
Long lay the world
In sin and error pining
'Til he appeared
And the soul felt its worth
The thrill of hope…
Can't put you on an international flight.
We'll go to the safe house for now.
Where the fuck's all this traffic
coming from? Can we just drive?
Can you fucking drive
up on the curb, please?
- Sir, think about your protection.
- Fuck that.
I got people smarter than you
telling me I can't be protected.
If they want to find me, they'll find me.
I can go over there
and get scared to death,
or I can sit the fuck here
and be scared to death.
These people will kill you.
We need to get you out of the city.
I am not going anywhere
until he finds my son.
O night divine
O night
When Christ was born
Oh, oh night…
Hey. Hey!
Fall on your knees…
Wait! Don't.
-O hear the angel voices
-Please.
O night divine
- O night…
- Hello.
I flew halfway across the world
to identify my child.
Now, I'm coming for yours.
Who's this?
A parent, just like you.
O night divine
Hey! Get the fuck off me!
O night
O night divine
Fuck it. To the back, right away.
Get to work on it.
Raul. I want to talk to you.
- Who the fuck?
- What's up?
- Don't do that.
- Whoa.
Are you fucking serious?
Is that how you run?
What the fuck is that about?
What have you got there?
- What the fuck are you holding?
- I wasn't running. I really...
What the fuck are these, man?
All right. Where are they?
They didn't tell me.
- They didn't tell you? Don't lie to me.
- No, sir.
- I'm not lying, man.
- Do I look like I was born yesterday?
- No, sir. No.
- How'd she get a passport from you?
- You fucking this kid?
- What?
- Fucking a girl half your age?
- Come on. She's a kid.
- Are you fucking a kid?
- Fuck you, man!
I told you she's like my kid.
I raised her.
So you do know this kid.
You're lying to me.
I'm not lying.
I told you she's like my kid.
So do you realize your kid
is in a lot of trouble?
She didn't do what they say she did.
She was just at the wrong...
Yeah, I know the story.
Wrong place, wrong fucking time.
I'm going to be honest with you,
all right?
Okay.
She will not get out
of this fucking city alive.
Not without my help.
Mm?
Who the hell are you?
I'm a fucking cop!
- Okay. I understood that.
- You understand?
- Yes.
- All right.
I understand.
I happen to have a vested interest
in this guy, Charlie. You know Charlie?
They didn't tell me where they went.
I swear. She said she'd call me.
- That's all I...
- She would call you?
That's dishonest.
- Come on, bro. I...
- You're dishonest. Quiet.
Unlock the phone.
Unlock the fucking phone.
Unlock it.
Here, man.
You need the girl to stay alive, right?
Mia, right?
- Please, yeah. Mia's her name.
- Hm? All right.
- I'm gonna help you.
- I appreciate that.
This is how it works.
When I leave here, you do not know me.
You have not seen me. We did not talk.
I have not seen you. I don't know you.
We didn't talk. None of that shit.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Are we cool?
- We're good, man.
All right. We're cool.
Hands up! Turn around, face the wall!
- Put your hands up! He's got a gun!
- I got it.
No! I don't have a gun!
- Where's the gun, asshole?
- I don't have a fucking gun!
Where's the fucking gun?
Hold him the fuck down.
Where were you
the night my son was killed?
He dismissed me
because I disagreed with him.
I warned him not to do a deal
with Beaumont's son.
He refused to listen. I had to obey.
Who's the girl?
Charlie Beaumont's girlfriend.
She stole a car from Master Tsui.
He caught her and kept her in his debt.
Shouldn't be hard to flush her out...
Boss.
- What is it?
- There's a guy. He wants to see you.
What the fuck you want, man?
I…
I just wanted you to know
that I wasn't in that room with them.
Yeah, I... I know who your son is.
I swear, I was just a guy sitting in a car
on the other side of the street.
You know? I had nothing to do
with what went down.
These guys showed up, and in two minutes,
everything just got fucked up.
Oh no. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Please, please. Okay.
This... The girl. Please.
The girl… The girl…
I know where the girl's gonna be at.
If you let me live, I can take you to her.
Where?
It's just a temporary slide
Back in the abyss
I should've seen it coming…
Open armed
In a thick coat of structure
Shielding me
From my own blades and dagger
There was purpose on the horizon
The shrinking hours of light
Are gray and feeble
The soggy trees sigh
Dropping their leaves in defeat
The temperature falls
The big lights switch on
And from time to time
Fireworks frighten the cats
Don't give a shit. It's five bucks.
Are you serious?
Five bucks for all these underage girls?
Jesus. Five bucks.
I don't want it. I don't need it.
- Oh shit.
- Uh-uh-uh.
Where's Charlie?
Look, I'm a cop,
but I'm not here to arrest you, all right?
I'm not trying to put you away.
I work for his father.
But if you are concerned at all
for his well-being, which I doubt,
then you will just tell me
where the fuck he is.
I'm not telling you shit.
Ah, that's real stupid, all right?
That's the wrong fucking answer!
Now whatever hustle this is,
whatever you and your uncle,
whatever scheme you got going on,
you are getting paid, right?
I will just pay you double,
and then you can have this back,
and you get to fucking walk away.
- You think I'm with Charlie for the money?
- I don't give a fuck why!
Fuck you! If you're not here to arrest me,
then get the fuck away from me!
Oh shit.
- That's him.
- That's who?
That's the guy that killed Tsui.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm fucking sure.
He was wearing a hockey mask
until I shot it off.
Nah, you know what? Fuck this. I'm out.
You stay exactly where you are.
You do not move.
Yo.
What brings you boys here?
We didn't want to miss out on all the fun.
I didn't know you played hockey.
We just want to talk to the girl.
Come on, Walker. She's a suspect.
You with us?
I'm not. That all right?
There gonna be a problem?
I'll give you two guesses.
You go that way. You, with me.
Walker, I've asked nice.
Now, I'm taking her.
I don't think so.
You can step aside
and let us take the girl in,
or we'll just go through you.
Up to you.
All right, that's far enough.
Shit.
Hey! Hey!
Move it, bitch.
Get the fuck off me, man!
No!
Mia!
Mia?
Hey. It's okay. I got you.
Let's get out of here. Okay. Fuck!
I'm here to get you. Your father sent me.
- Man, fuck you!
- Charlie!
No, no!
It ain't up for discussion.
Get up!
- Tío!
- Let her go!
Drop the gun, Raul.
Get up. Come on, let's go.
Hands in the air.
- Put the knife down! Now!
- Drop your weapon!
- I'm a cop!
I'm telling you, drop your gun, man!
Drop it!
I don't give a fuck who you are!
Charlie! Charlie, help me!
Look at my badge, you dumb motherfucker!
I'm a cop.
Johnny!
No, no, Mia! Mia, no! Wait! Mia!
No, wait! No! Tío. What?
Come on. We gotta go!
Tío, come on, please!
No! No!
No, please, please!
Tío! No! No, come on, no!
No! No, no, no! No, no! Charlie!
Come on!
Need backup!
Come on, come on!
Get in. Come on.
Charlie.
Get the fuck in.
Let's go!
Get down!
- Help me tie them up!
- Down! Get down now!
No, no!
Hayes?
Man, what the fuck do we do now?
Please stand behind the yellow line.
Walker, what the...
Hey, Ellie, you near any cops right now?
Only the entire fucking force.
What have you done?
All right. All right, listen to me.
Vincent, Hayes, Jake,
they're all involved, all right?
They weren't in pursuit
of the fucking truck,
they were after the coke inside it.
They're the ones that shot up Tsui's.
Demons in fucking hockey masks.
- Ellie?
- Hayes is dead.
All right.
All right, I need you
to go to the hospital.
Sorry, what?
I need you to get to the hospital,
all right?
Cortez, I don't think he was involved,
and if he is, then he'll say something.
How can you be so sure?
Because he's my friend.
I don't think I can do this.
Ellie, do you remember
when you asked me why didn't I trust you?
This is me, right now, I am trusting you.
Please, can you just do this for me?
Ellie?
Where are you taking them?
I swear to God, wherever I get to,
I'll call you straightaway.
Just please get to the hospital.
- Do this for me, please.
- Okay.
Thank you.
I'll have to call you back.
Don't you fucking hang up on me,
you little prick.
Listen, about an hour ago,
I ran into our friend at a club,
but I didn't get to talk to her
because a bunch
of yourDynasty Warriorbuddies showed up.
- No, they weren't my buddies.
- They sure looked it.
Vincent, I don't have to tell you
how important it is
that you find those kids before they do.
No shit.
Where are they now?
That's the thing. I got no idea.
All I know is I got that stuff you wanted.
So, where should we meet?
My buyer doesn't want the coke anymore.
Too much heat. All thanks to you.
Ching, I swear to God, I will put a hole
through your fucking chest.
Tell me, how many times
are you going to fuck up, Vincent?
I tip you off about the girl,
and you let her go.
I tell you about the shipments.
All you had to do
was intercept the fucking truck.
So, what the fuck did...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Where is the gratitude?
I got you a promotion.
That was never part of our deal.
Ching, we close this tonight,
or I have my boys
pimping dime bags in Chinatown.
Might make Mom suspicious,
don't you think?
Well done. You really played me.
But don't forget, this is my world,
and once I get what I'm due,
I'll fuck you up.
Listen to me.
You got one hour.
We all have loose ends, Vincent.
Where are you?
You be careful.
Detective Cheung.
Here to see a patient, Officer Cortez.
Sure, let me check that for you.
- What floor is that? What floor is he on?
- Third floor.
Notify security. Now!
Freeze!
I said, freeze! Let her go.
Fuck you, cop!
You want her? You really want her?
You can fucking have her.
Shit.
Don't fucking move.
Get up.
Okay.
- What?
- Get in the car.
All right. Sit down here.
You got a first aid kit in the cabinet,
below the sink.
Let me take a look what you got here.
Oh Jesus, did she try to fix that?
Jesus fucking Christ.
We'd be halfway to where we're going
if we had papers.
- Yeah? Where's that exactly?
- Why? So you can tell him?
No, so I can get you a surgeon
so you don't fucking die.
Yo, Lawrence. Listen, I got Charlie.
I sent you a location
where to find him, okay?
That's it. Deal closed.
Come get him. You hear me?
Lawrence?
Lawrence, you there?
Shit.
Mrs. Walker? I'm Detective Cheung.
- Patrick doesn't live here anymore.
- I understand that. It, um…
What happened?
I'm trying to get hold of him,
and he's not answering his phone.
He has this place, down by the lake.
It's his father's old cabin.
Ching told me our sons were friends once.
I didn't know that.
Perhaps they had us in common.
Parents they were trying to escape.
I guess that's why they found each other.
My son Charlie
never forgave me for his mother's death.
I couldn't…
Make him understand how hard it was
for me to watch her suffer.
I would have done anything
to keep my son safe.
I trust you would do the same.
Feels like something's missing.
What's missing?
- The buyer.
- That's right, the buyer.
Ching, where's the fucking buyer?
On his way.
Freeze!
Don't even fucking try it.
You don't look much like a cop killer.
Hard to tell you're a cop in the dark.
What now?
We're leaving.
Going to Lawrence isn't an option for us.
What you got in your hand, Charlie?
Hey!
Come to me! Come to me!
Go, go, go!
Go, go!
- Charlie!
- No, Mia! Mia, no!
No!
Mia!
Stop! Fuck you!
No! Charlie!
Charlie?
Charlie.
I'm dealing with this, son.
You just… you just let me handle it.
Your son…
…took the one thing I loved in this world.
- No! No, please don't!
- Wait! No! Please, no!
It's only fair you do the same to him.
No.
Yeah.
No! No, please don't! It's a lie!
- I'm sorry, son.
- No, Dad, stop!
- It wasn't us. I didn't kill anybody!
- Please, no!
- Hold her still.
- It wasn't us, it was the cops!
- Hold her still. Hold her still.
- Listen to me.
- Hold her still! Hold her still!
- No!
You can't do this.
You can't do this! Please don't.
Please, don't fucking do this.
Don't fucking do this to me again, Dad!
- Look at me, Dad. Look at me.
- Charlie, what are you doing?
- You shoot her, you gotta shoot me, Dad.
- Move out of the way!
You fucking hear me?
You shoot her, you shoot through me!
- Please!
- Shoot through me!
- Do it.
- Shoot through me, Dad. Can you do it?
- I promised your mom I'd take care of you.
- Now!
No, Dad. Listen to me.
Dad, please, I can't lose anybody else!
I can't lose anymore!
I can't lose anymore.
I can't… I can't.
Put your weapons down!
Your guns, put them down!
They didn't kill your son.
You've been chasing the wrong people.
Gun.
You betrayed my son?
Bullshit!
You betrayed me first!
When Big Brother died,
it was supposed to be my time.
But you put that kid in charge
instead of me.
I warned you
your son wasn't ready to lead!
So you had him killed?
No!
It was these motherfuckers.
They killed him.
I didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
You ungrateful traitor…
You killed my son!
You okay?
You okay? Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm okay.
Look at you.
You've grown.
Take care of her.
I will, Dad. I will.
Dad?
Dad.
Come on, Charlie. We gotta go.
Come on, baby, we gotta go.
Come on, go. We gotta go.
Don't do it.
Why couldn't you just let me
get on that train?
What the fuck difference
does it make to you?!
You don't get to walk away from this.
Jesus Christ, Walker.
You don't get to fucking backpedal.
Not after what you've done.
I ain't gonna run no more.
I'm proud of you.
You can do the time for both of us.
Don't make me put you down, Vince.
Fuck you, Walker.
We all know what you've done.
Nah.
Only you.
There are still people out there
looking for you.
- You'd be safer if you turn yourselves in.
- We'll take our chances.
Is he gonna be okay?
I don't know.
What now?
Now you should arrest me.
You're a good cop, Ellie.
I probably should've been nicer to you.
I'll make sure she gets it.
Your daughter.
I'll take the present to her.
No.
I don't want to ruin her Christmas.